[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
Mr. Fang
What if the glasses fall in the water?
Shut up.
Got it! I got it!
Go ahead and say it. I've forgiven you.
Now look what you've done.
You set fire to all my Grandpa's grandpas
and burned them all.
I have to send you over there
to explain this to them.
In case you don't recognize my Grandpa,
I need to tell you
what my Grandpa was like.
My Grandpa,
he was a kind and happy little old man.
And then?
Grandpa's gone.
Where did he go?
He drowned.
That's not right.
Didn't you say Grandpa could swim
ten laps on a single breath?
He took a breath halfway.
Don't you get that?
But that's not the point!
The point is... The point is...
The point is, if Grandpa
hadn't gotten a leg cramp,
he definitely could've swum ten laps.
The point is, you must cherish life.
My Grandpa tried to save someone else
and sacrificed his own life.
If you don't cherish your life,
you're letting my Grandpa down.
Bro, I mean no offense,
but I just feel like
the example you gave earlier
is a bit extreme.
If things are like you said,
then there are tons of people in the world
letting your Grandpa down every day.
Fine. Then I'll save whoever I can.
Bring the ice.
You don't cherish your life.
Is that fair to my Grandpa?
Why the ice cubes?
To help you cool down, get it?
Makes sense. Makes sense. Makes sense.
Bro, I was wrong.
I... I admit
I was a bit over the top.
But if I may be so bold... I...
I... I think the example you gave
is still a bit extreme.
Because as a human being,
we have the right to decide our own fate?
So if I choose to give up my life...
You can't choose to give up your life.
Giving up your life hurts others.
I'd be dead.
Who could I possibly hurt?
Me.
And you call yourself a man of culture?
You can't even grasp this basic logic?
Let me tell you my story.
Take a good look.
What's wrong? Don't recognize me?
Is this...
some kind of door-to-door service?
This is my boss, Brother Bin.
I'm sorry.
The famous local Great Benefactor.
I know.
Then you should explain... to the boss,
to Brother Great Benefactor...
Explain yourself.
Back then... I didn't bully you.
I didn't want to hurt you.
I didn't want to sleep with you, okay?
Do you know,
when you offered to spend 20,000 yuan
to buy me for a night,
just how insulting that was to me?
At the time... I didn't... I...
I already wanted to die back then.
I just wanted some warmth.
I wanted a hug.
I wanted you to hold me.
Just a simple, innocent hug.
I didn't!
20,000 yuan for a hug?
Is that innocent?
Was it too much?
I'm sorry.
My story
actually starts ten years ago.
He said, since passing the corner florist
and forgetting to get you
a bouquet of white roses,
I knew right then.
On this train of love,
I should get off at the next stop
and chase my own freedom.
You're three months pregnant.
You didn't even know?
Doctor,
can I get an abortion?
Miss, come back!
Miss, live a good life.
Keep living.
You young people...
You really don't take life seriously.
If you don't live your life well,
you... you'd be letting this old man down.
Okay.
Grandpa Zhao gave me my life.
So I must cherish my own life.
But your life
was given by your mom.
If you give up your own life,
how can you face your mom?
My mom ran off right after she had me.
So having a mom or not
to me,
isn't all that important.
Giving birth is a mother's hardest task.
He doesn't cherish life.
He doesn't cherish life,
and he doesn't respect his mom.
We should let him experience
the pain a mother feels during childbirth.
I looked it up.
Artificial Intelligence says
electric shocks can generally match
the pain of childbirth.
What? Electric welding?
No, you even believe an idiot?
Brother.
Give it to me.
Bro, you... Coming!
My waist!
You can't even handle this much pain?
Your mom hurt way more when she had you!
My mother and I...
never discussed if it hurt, bro!
You disrespect life, disrespect me,
and disrespect Grandpa Zhao!
Why zap me when the story's done?
Hold on.
What's her zapping me got to do with you?
Let me tell you my story.
I've been sickly since childhood.
Hold on, hold on!
Actually, you don't need to
start from the bicycle.
You...
Fast forward a bit.
Skip to the ending.
What was the result?
Open-chest surgery three times.
Four times in the Intensive Care Unit.
I have already found you
a suitable kidney donor.
Whose?
I can't tell you.
But...
he's a selfless, good person.
The doctor said I'd live to 25 at most.
I'm 30 this year.
Every minute, every second I live,
is hard-earned.
Do you know how much I envy
that you have such a healthy body?
Do you know that disrespecting Grandpa
is a huge insult to me?
is a huge insult to everyone
in this room?
I know, I get it!
Enough!
Thank you, Bie Fan.
Thanks, thanks, thanks!
I get it now.
Everyone in this yard has a story, huh?
Give me the stun baton.
Bie Fan.
What are you doing, Bie Fan?
I'm going to tell everyone my story!
No need, Fan! No need!
Your big bro already knows your story.
I'll tell them later.
How about you listen to your big bro?
Save some battery for your big bro.
Do you still want to die?
Do you?
I'm not dying anymore!
You've shocked me to a crisp!
Ease up a little, little bro.
I've figured it out.
If I do this, Brother.
If I... If I do this, I let everyone down.
I'm letting Grandpa down.
And the life he sacrificed for others.
And the good life he gave his life for.
I'm letting them down. I definitely am.
Also, I'm letting my mother down.
I'm letting every mother down.
Who endured agonizing pain,
Agonizing pain. Yes, agonizing pain.
To bring every life into this world.
I'm letting down my healthy body.
I'm letting it down. I absolutely am.
I've decided not to die.
Didn't you hear me?
I've decided
Not to die.
I've made up my mind.
Our country's beautiful landscapes,
I haven't traveled them yet.
The great peaks of our nation,
I haven't even been to them.
I haven't scuba dived on Hainan Island.
I haven't been skiing in Altay.
I haven't even spent New Year in Sanya.
Starting today,
I will sleep early and wake up early.
Every morning when I wake up,
Black coffee on an empty stomach.
I'll train my body.
I'll work out.
I'll do chest presses, then squats.
Do cardio three times a week.
I'll learn English.
Learn English, learn street dance.
Saturdays, Sundays I'll—
I'll even learn the drums.
Sounds good.
Start dating.
Right, I gotta start dating. Start dating.
I'll, right, take it seriously.
Right, take it seriously.
Find myself a great partner.
In this life,
I have to love passionately at least once.
I want to taste food from all over China.
Where to first? Let me think.
Go to Xi- go, go, go.
Go to Tianjin for some steamed buns.
Go to Xinjiang.
Go to Xinjiang for hand-pulled noodles.
Go back to the Northeast.
Back to the Northeast for grilled kidneys.
I'll go to Sichuan.
Go to Sichuan for some Ye'erba.
I declare,
I've thought it over.
I was being an idiot.
Bro,
I'm hungry.
Brother.
Here, brother.
Drink up! Here.
Here, here.
Come on, let me say a few words.
Brother is speaking! Good!
Then I'll say a few words.
I really had no idea.
I mean, just washing a car,
and I run into a dying man.
After bringing him over here,
Everyone wrote a little essay.
And we even saved a vibrant life!
You're a bit too vibrant, aren't you?
And you're already eating!
Why don't you say a few words?
Say no more.
To Grandpa!
Well,
speaking of Grandpa...
I just remembered something.
Grandpa just came to me in a dream.
He said, "Anything you do is fine,
but you shouldn't have used the stun baton
to zap that poor kid!"
I regret it so much!
I don't think Grandpa is right.
Edison invented alternating current.
Brother used electricity to talk to me.
My parents gave birth to me.
Brother gave me a second life, so...
Brother...
S-sorry about that.
Brother is my Second parents!
To Brother!
Say no more.
Well said!
Right on!
Mr. Fang.
No need, sit down, sit down.
For what I did the other day,
the bad things...
I apologize, little brother.
I'm sorry.
Brother!
Lean your forehead over here.
This... this...
Brother loves you! Brother loves...
Brother loves me.
I love Brother too!
Slow down, slow down. Easy, easy.
A fight makes the best of friends.
Come on, let's drink!
You're a great brother to me!
You are...
Grandpa!
You are my Second parents!
I'll dedicate an old song to Brother.
Just listen to me.
Just stay here, and that's it.
Brother.
I have lots to handle back home, Brother.
Alright then. I'll drive you.
No, Brother. No need to see us out.
Please don't see us out, Brother.
We'll just stroll back.
A nice walk will help me digest.
Alright.
Then take this...
Take this stuff. Take it.
What's all this for?
What for?
Come back often to see me and Grandpa.
I must come back often just for Grandpa.
Don't worry, Brother.
I'll miss you.
Love you, Brother! Love you!
Come back!
Love you! Love you!
Come back! Come back! Come back!
Come back!
Love you guys, big bro's boys!
Brothers, we're off!
Goodbye, Brother!
Come visit often!
Bye-bye!
Brother, can you slow down a bit?
I can't keep up with you.
Who are you calling brother?
How could you throw it away?
Brother! Brother! Brother!
Where is this brother?
Where's this brother at?
Who's your brother?
Where's the suicide note?
What do you want the suicide note for?
None of your business.
Come on, give me the suicide note.
Do you still want to die?
I'll do whatever I want.
It has nothing to do with you.
Come on, give me the note.
Give me the note.
Brother Bin!
Mr. Fang... Mr. Fang, Mr. Fang, Mr. Fang!
Where's the note?
Aren't you all better now?
What do you mean better?
I lied to you, and you believed it?
Shock me. Right, right.
Shock me! Shock me! Shock me!
You're shocking me! Shocking me, right?
You're shocking me!
Where's the note?
I'm going to tell Brother Bin.
You're telling Brother Bin?
Who is your Brother Bin?
They're just a bunch of criminals.
They use vigilante justice.
And you're their accomplice.
"A mother's greatest pain is childbirth."
Come here, let me see.
How does it hurt?
Does it hurt? Does it hurt? Does it hurt?
It hurts!
Give me the note! Give it to me!
When drawing the bow,
I lock my eyes on the bullseye.
For this moment,
I've waited too long.
So much so that
my eyes magnify the bullseye 1,000 times,
so much so that
a canyon is carved between my brows,
my chest
is cracked by my pounding heart.
Release.
I have no arrows.
Because
I shot myself.
Mr. Fang!
Is anyone there?
Is anybody out there?!
Hello? Is anyone here?
How did you get in?